<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916070500 +0000" stop="20250916080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Coffin Corner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon gets hired to be a bodyguard for a courier of securities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916080500 +0000" stop="20250916090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In Hawaii (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In Hawaii, J.R. is framed for murder and thrown in jail by a vengeful cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916090000 +0000" stop="20250916093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Shooting Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday lands in hot water after a thief he attempted to apprehend, and in the process shot at, turns up dead and SID can't find evidence that the man fired at Friday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916093000 +0000" stop="20250916100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Three con artists have been swindling businessmen from out of town by posing as a prostitute and two policemen. The detectives set a trap as Gannon pretends to be a manufacturer from Lincoln, Nebraska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916100000 +0000" stop="20250916103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 172 -- Boy...the Things You Do For The Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After Malloy gives a gorgeous wealthy blonde a traffic ticket, she stalks him, affecting him and the police force. Although uninterested in her, Malloy is forced to "take one" for the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916103000 +0000" stop="20250916110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 92 -- Tell Him He Pushed Back A Little Too Hard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed respond to repeated calls about an argument between two men and their wives over a boat they co-own. The feud escalates and ends with a fatal conclusion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916110000 +0000" stop="20250916120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Secret Age Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony's new podcast sets out to finally uncover the truth about Mr. Quizzer's real age."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916120000 +0000" stop="20250916123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Three Boys And A Burro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Gilbert and Richard find a burro for sale in Mayfield and they each decide to go in $10 for it. After getting their parent's permission, Richard and Gilbert fight over who gets to keep the burro, which they name Pepe. However, once they get a load of just how destructive a burro can be, they dump the problem of room and board on Beaver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916123000 +0000" stop="20250916130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie Quits School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie pompously announces that he's dropping out of school to get a high paying job at a gas station. However, all is not as it seems when Wally and Lumpy get a glance at Eddie's new free spending life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916130000 +0000" stop="20250916140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Gilded Lily</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Enid Griffin, the secretary of Stewart Brent, attempts to commit suicide after learning her boss has married. Arthur Binney attempts to blackmail Stewart Brent with facts about his new wife having been in jail for fraud. When Binny turns up dead, Brent is framed for his murder, but confesses to protect his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916140000 +0000" stop="20250916150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Blackmailer  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Cartoonist Ron Winfield has been keeping Atlanta enthralled with his recent storyline involving a Senator's affair. But just before the woman in the affair is named in print, the strips disappear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916150000 +0000" stop="20250916160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Accused</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba tries to rescue a woman from a rapist, but she mistakes him for her attacker. Gillespie tangles with an ambitious district attorney who plans to use the case to further his career.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916160000 +0000" stop="20250916170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Moonshiner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Boone Walton returns after he was convicted of moon-shining andJason promises to keep watch on him</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916170000 +0000" stop="20250916180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Baker's Dozen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Three baby boys are born on a stagecoach that arrives in Dodge just after being robbed. Their mother dies and Doc fights to keep the boys together instead of going to an orphanage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916180000 +0000" stop="20250916190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Kingdom Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights and Candy are captured by a man known as "The Judge," who turns them into slaves, forcing them to work in his gold mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916190000 +0000" stop="20250916193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is baffled when the marshal of a neighboring town refuses to hold a gambler who just attempted murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916193000 +0000" stop="20250916200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem At Mission Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mark is paralyzed, Lucas attempts to cure him at the mission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916200000 +0000" stop="20250916210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Duke Shannon Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>"With his clever tall tales, old prospector Henry Shannon talks Charlie Wooster into coming with him to search for a gold mine. When Hawks finds out about this, he rides out after the two men, along with Shannon's grandson Duke. Also following the old men are three men who hope to grab the gold for themselves."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916210000 +0000" stop="20250916220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Insanity Epidemic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Stanley freaks out when he learns one of his past captains is now his Battalion Chief, causing the others to worry about his increased paranoia. Two men’s carelessness starts a fire at a gas station. A new hospital administrator causes problems. A woman accidentally shoots her husband with a nail gun. Two clowns start a fight at an ice rink. A car leaves an overpass and crashes into a transfer truck filled with pesticides.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916220000 +0000" stop="20250916223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Billfold Syndrome</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles becomes so irate when he is turned down for a future medical position at home that he refuses to talk to anyone in the unit, until Hawkeye and B.J. send him a false telegram from home. Meanwhile, a young soldier, Jerry Wilson, can't remember his own identity, so Sidney Freedman is called for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916223000 +0000" stop="20250916230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>None Like It Hot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As the temperatures reach triple digits, Hawkeye and B.J. receive their new rubber bathtub from Abercrombie &amp; Fitch. However, soon the whole camp is hot under the collar as word leaks out about the tub and everyone wants a dip, except for Klinger, who is trying to get his Section 8 by wearing a fur coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916230000 +0000" stop="20250916233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>They Call The Wind Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A strong windstorm affects the M*A*S*H personnel in varying ways: Hawkeye and most of the unit busy themselves securing items that could blow away; Radar prepares his animal hutch for the worst; a disgusted Charles switches his Tokyo-leave transportation from air to ground and runs into a difficult medical situation en route to Seoul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916233000 +0000" stop="20250917000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Ego</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Tom Greenleigh of "Stars and Stripes" comes to the 4077th to write an article about Charles, which makes him act even more egotistical than usual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917000000 +0000" stop="20250917003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And His Merry Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie and his friends find a hungry man in the woods who tells them the story of Robin Hood, the boys begin to steal for the man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917003000 +0000" stop="20250917010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Cave Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is the laughingstock of the town after he mistakes the owner of the Mayberry Bank as a robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917010000 +0000" stop="20250917013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Reserve Program</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is getting ready to enter the reserves, and the Clampetts are giving him a party, with gifts, including lady fingers, a squirrel rifle and a Confederate uniform. Jethro heads down to the reserve where they are preparing to shoot a Civil War movie. The men there think Jethro is an actor for the movie. Jethro soon thinks that the Civil War is going to happen again and rushes home to tell Granny and Elly. Granny decides to take up the fight to make sure the South wins, again, since she is convinced they won the first time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917013000 +0000" stop="20250917020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Groom For Sergeant Carter's Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter objects to the man with whom his sister is engaged, and uses Gomer as a means of breaking them up. Little does he know, the brother-in-law-to-be also is a Marine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917020000 +0000" stop="20250917023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Impersonation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Schultz to portray Klink in order to free three of his men whom the Gestapo has captured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917023000 +0000" stop="20250917030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Pizza Parlor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>To get a Italian officer to defect, Hogan and the gang use pizza to tempt him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917030000 +0000" stop="20250917033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Peggy Lee And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Peggy Lee and Tim Conway. Originally aired on 03/30/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917033000 +0000" stop="20250917043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Missing Button</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's campaign to prove his estranged wife an unfit mother is interrupted when he's arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917043500 +0000" stop="20250917050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Rites Of Jeff Myrtlebank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man comes back to life at his own funeral and soon begins to act very strangely.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917050500 +0000" stop="20250917053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Party Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman shares a party line with two nosy neighbors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917053500 +0000" stop="20250917060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Cell 227</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E34</episode-num>
    <desc>An innocent man faces death in the gas chamber for the death of a girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917060500 +0000" stop="20250917070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Light And Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix gets involved in the case of a millionaire's wife accused of killing the boyfriend of her stepdaughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917070500 +0000" stop="20250917080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Perfect Fit For A Frame</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon gets hired to protect a girl but when her supposed pursuer is found dead he finds himself charged with murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917080500 +0000" stop="20250917090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In Hawaii (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In Hawaii, J.R. is framed for murder and thrown in jail by a vengeful cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917090000 +0000" stop="20250917093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Jobs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A nervy bank robber uses innocent women to help commit his crimes. Friday and Gannon are nearly sidetracked when one of the victims lies about her involvement and later proves to have a criminal record of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917093000 +0000" stop="20250917100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill invites Joe to dinner and a football game at his home in Eagle Rock. The only problem: Gannon's neighbors keep interrupting the visit with petty and then not-so-petty problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917100000 +0000" stop="20250917103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 22: So This Little Guy Goes Into This Bar, And...</sub-title>
    <desc>"A fur burglary, a family fight and a loud party."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917103000 +0000" stop="20250917110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 15 -- Exactly One Hundred Yards</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On their day off, Malloy and Reed agree to give a talk to a group of fifth grade students, and then offer to let the kids watch them train for the California Police Olympics. But when the tires of their patrol car are slashed and a stopwatch goes missing out of reed's car, the two officers start to suspect one of the children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917110000 +0000" stop="20250917120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mysterious Locations</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit some of the most mysterious places on earth."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917120000 +0000" stop="20250917123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally Stays At Lumpy's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A communication gap ensues when Wally wants to spend the night at Lumpy's and Beaver wants to have Gilbert spend the night. Beaver asks June and she tells him he can sometime when Wally spends the night somewhere and Wally asks Ward, who tells him he can sometime when Beaver has someone spend the night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917123000 +0000" stop="20250917130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Laundry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver agrees to help Richard cart his family's clothes down to the laundromat; however, half way there they discover that Richard has lost the three dollars his mother gave him. This leads him to ask Beaver if he could use the Cleaver washer. They soon find themselves in another jam when the washing machine overflows after Beaver put in too much soap and starch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917130000 +0000" stop="20250917140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lazy Lover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Attempting to miss hitting her stepfather's car, Patricia Faxon swerves as she enters her driveway and hits the hedges. After asking her stepfather, Bertrand Allred, to move his car, he finds Bob Fleetwood badly hurt next to the hedges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917140000 +0000" stop="20250917150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cookie Monster  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a cookie mogul is found dead after announcing plans to take over a number of baking companies, Matlock works the defense for another cookie maker suspected in the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917150000 +0000" stop="20250917160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Fifteen Forever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Sparta grieves after a drunk driver causes a fatal crash with high school cheerleaders on their way home from a game. While the officers try to find other driver, Althea tries to help the victim's families deal with their loss. The accident brings back painful memories for retired officer Tom Dugan. Meanwhile, district attorney Dutton accuses the department of being inadequate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917160000 +0000" stop="20250917170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Obsession</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen starts taking pills to stay awake, and then to sleep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917170000 +0000" stop="20250917180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Wishbone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt goes after three bandits who robbed a stagecoach and killed the driver and guard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917180000 +0000" stop="20250917190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>An Earthquake Called Callahan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe searches for a professional fighter who can clear the name of an incarcerated Dusty Rhoades.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917190000 +0000" stop="20250917193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>New arrival Mario Arsatti becomes very friendly with Lucas, but this turns out to be merely pleasure before business: he's been hired to kill Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917193000 +0000" stop="20250917200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Old Man Running (aka The Wanted Man)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas, who blames his wife's death on his father-in-law, refuses to help the old man elude gunmen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917200000 +0000" stop="20250917210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Will Santee Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>"The Santee family---Will, his mother, and his younger sister---join the wagon train under a false surname. They have been forced out of town after town because of a terrible thing a family member did. They confide in Hale, Hawks, and Charlie, who agree to keep their secret from the others on the train. But it soon comes out anyway, and things get complicated when Will falls for a young woman from the wagon train."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917210000 +0000" stop="20250917220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A sporadic electrical short plagues the squad but Roy and John are convinced they can fix it. A back-to-nature couple is ordered to cut back on their shrubbery; the wife is discovered to have a variant of anthrax. The paramedics rescue a man trapped at the top of a tower.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917220000 +0000" stop="20250917223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Baby, It's Cold Outside</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>While everyone is complaining about the record cold snap, Charles becomes the most unpopular man in camp, when his parents send him a winterized polar suit that he insists on flaunting in front of everyone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917223000 +0000" stop="20250917230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In this unique episode, the camera becomes the eyes of a young wounded soldier. It records his sensory responses to being wounded, flown by helicopter to the 4077th, examined, operated on and treated in post-operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917230000 +0000" stop="20250917233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Comrade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. discover that Charles is living the "life of Riley," thanks to the attentions of his menially paid Korean servant, Comrade Park, a man of unusual skills. He has an important contribution to make—a native remedy for a seemingly insoluble medical problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917233000 +0000" stop="20250918000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Gas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Heavy casualties are arriving, creating severe problems for the M*A*S*H unit because they are nearly out of Pentothal. Mulcahy takes up a collection from everyone—including a case of wine from Charles' private supply—and he and Charles take the jeep to make a trade with the black marketers for Pentothal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918000000 +0000" stop="20250918003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie's Pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy pays attention to a fatherless new boy in town, which makes Opie jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918003000 +0000" stop="20250918010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee The Crusader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee and most of the women in town rally against Andy when he tries to evict a much-beloved butter and egg man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918010000 +0000" stop="20250918013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lafe Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is looking for a beau for his gorgeous daughter, so Drysdale and Jane set Elly up with Fred Penrod, a young accountant at the bank. However, no one can seem to get his name straight. Meanwhile, Lafe Crick returns to plant a paw-paw tree in the back yard, really to look for the Clampett fortune he still believes is buried in the back yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918013000 +0000" stop="20250918020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Minds His Sergeant's Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter asks Gomer to drive his car straight home from the airport after dropping him off. But sure enough, the car gets stolen, and Gomer has just one day to find it—or suffer the consequences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918020000 +0000" stop="20250918023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The 43rd, A Moving Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Plans to destroy an anti-aircraft battery are upset by Klink's new executive officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918023000 +0000" stop="20250918030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Cook A German Goose By Radar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A new prisoner in a corporal's uniform turns out to be a general with a mission for Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918030000 +0000" stop="20250918033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nanette Fabray And Michele Lee</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nanette Fabray and Michele Lee. Originally aired on 04/13/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918033000 +0000" stop="20250918043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Paper Bullets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is caught between rival political families when the wife of a campaigning senator is accused of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918043500 +0000" stop="20250918050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>To Serve Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kanamits, nine-foot-tall aliens, arrive on Earth with one lofty goal: To Serve Man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918050500 +0000" stop="20250918053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Schartz-metterklume Method</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a governess at the Wellington household has surprising results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918053500 +0000" stop="20250918060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of Credit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A researcher comes to a small-town bank to find out what happened at a robbery years earlier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918060500 +0000" stop="20250918070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Odds Against Donald Jordan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to find missing building contractor Donald Jordan. He gets poor help from the man's partner, wife and sister. Each offers a different reason for his disappearance. When Jordan reappears, he assures Mannix that he's fine and asks him to drop the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918070500 +0000" stop="20250918080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On The Hill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A military general hires Cannon to find the daughter he put up for adoption years ago but it appears as though someone doesn't want the girl to be found.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918080500 +0000" stop="20250918090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Desperate Pursuit, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty's testimony in a trial puts herself in danger and gives her attention from an impressed reporter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918090000 +0000" stop="20250918093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Frustration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carl Maxwell, a frustrated fellow detective, goes AWOL; Friday and Gannon have three days to track him down before Maxwell loses his badge for good.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918093000 +0000" stop="20250918100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Senior Citizen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of daring daylight house burglaries are taking place perpetrated by an octogenarian who uses the wedding and obituary notices in the paper to select his victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918100000 +0000" stop="20250918103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 153 -- Find Me A Needle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for the "Mulholland Mauler," who has raped six female hitchhikers and left them for dead. They quickly make an arrest of a likely suspect and take him to the location of an abandoned vehicle, after learning its owner never made it to her destination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918103000 +0000" stop="20250918110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 52 -- Good Cop: Handle With Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed see a man passed out in an alley and stop to lend assistance, deliver bad news to a young wife, apprehend a mentally ill man who then becomes uncontrollably violent in their patrol car, and respond to a robbery that needlessly becomes a tragedy. All along the way the officers have their every move second guessed by a pair of young, unethical freelance journalists who are determined to document police brutality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918110000 +0000" stop="20250918120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mystery Flavors</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918120000 +0000" stop="20250918123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy's Car Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward allows his car to be driven by Lumpy, who must get Eddie, Wally and Beaver to a sporting event in a neighboring town. However, on the way back, Lumpy disobeys Ward's orders and takes a shortcut home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918123000 +0000" stop="20250918130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Baby-sitter</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Wally has a previous engagement and is unable to babysit, Beaver fills in and quickly finds himself the object of a 10-year old's affection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918130000 +0000" stop="20250918140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Prodigal Parent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>When Philip Larkin, the owner of an import-export company, is murdered, his step-father, Joseph Harrison, is charged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918140000 +0000" stop="20250918150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Mother  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A mother confesses to a murder to protect her daughter, but Matlock soon sees through the ruse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918150000 +0000" stop="20250918160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Bug, Lady Bug</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>With the Chief in Quantico Bubba and Virgil try to catch a serial arsonist. Things get complicated after a man dies in one of the fires. And Councilwoman White stirs things up by appointing Tom Dugan acting chief of police in Gillespie's absence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918160000 +0000" stop="20250918170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Portrait</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Erin meets a painter who wants to paint her portrait.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918170000 +0000" stop="20250918180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bently</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Chester doubts a man's deathbed murder confession, so he sets out to find the real killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918180000 +0000" stop="20250918190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Grand Swing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben takes Jake on an extended tour of the Ponderosa to teach him a lesson after his recklessness destroys a wagon, killing a horse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918190000 +0000" stop="20250918193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Which Way'd They Go?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The notoriously lazy Jackman brothers discover their mortgage has been foreclosed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918193000 +0000" stop="20250918200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Old Tony</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and his girlfriend, Laurie, discover that an old hermit is very lonely.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918200000 +0000" stop="20250918210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jim Bridger Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>"An Army general announces he is taking over the wagon train and requiring all members to act as soldiers in helping him rescue a trapped cavalry garrison of 120 men who are otherwise likely to be slaughtered by hostile Utes. Flint, temporarily in charge of the wagon train, has little choice but to agree to the general's demand, as much as he hates it and his passengers want him to fight back. Particularly upsetting to Flint is learning that the man who recommended this takeover was Jim Bridger, a legendary frontiersman and scout who mostly raised Flint and whom he ..."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918210000 +0000" stop="20250918220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Family Ties</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy's mother-in-law is scheduled for her annual visit. A car runs into the back of a truck. Drs. Brackett and Early argue over attending a convention in Acapulco. An elderly man becomes ill from drinking a quack’s remedy. When a fire breaks out in a hospital room, the occupant goes into cardiac arrest. A boy’s model rocket sparks a house fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918220000 +0000" stop="20250918223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For A Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy takes being passed over for promotion philosophically until he hears of the rapid advancement made by a heroic helicopter pilot. Then his uncharacteristically bold actions stun Colonel Potter and the entire company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918223000 +0000" stop="20250918230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy writes a pre-Christmas letter to his sister, who is a nun. He recounts his frustrations at not being more effective at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918230000 +0000" stop="20250918233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>B.j. Papa San</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. almost becomes the surrogate father to a Korean family. Finding them a substitute for his own absent family, B.J. spends so much time with them that his medical efficiency begins to suffer, and Hawkeye worries about his health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918233000 +0000" stop="20250919000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Inga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It's instant attraction for Hawkeye when a beautiful Swedish doctor, called Inga, arrives to observe combat surgery. That is, until she upstages him in the operating room with a superior technique, and his ego is bruised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919000000 +0000" stop="20250919003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Sidecar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney comes back from a police auction with a motorcycle and sidecar. After he upsets the whole town with the conveyance, Andy has to find a way to convince Barney to give up the bike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919003000 +0000" stop="20250919010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Fair Ernest T. Bass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to make a silk purse out of a sow's ear when he takes it upon himself to turn Ernest T. into a presentable gentleman. The big test comes at Mrs. Wiley's weekly reception, at which Andy passes him off as his cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919010000 +0000" stop="20250919013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro In The Reserve</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny still believes she captured the real Ulysses S. Grant, still unsure that he is an actor in a movie. Granny also thinks that Colonel Blake is responsible for starting the second Civil War. Granny is upset at Blake, as well as Drysdale, for running away from battle. Drysdale tries to get in good with Granny by replacing Grant’s picture on the fifty-dollar bill with General Lee and tells her he captured Grant. Of course, she knows better.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919013000 +0000" stop="20250919020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer, The Peace Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When Bunny gets mad once again at Sgt. Carter, he sends Gomer in to explain what really happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919020000 +0000" stop="20250919023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Psychic Kommandant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink he has ESP in order to get the plans to a new airplane with a silent engine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919023000 +0000" stop="20250919030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Prince From The Phone Company</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>An African prince comes to Stalag 13 to negotiate with the Germans for the rights to build a submarine base in his country. Hogan replaces him with Kinchloe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919030000 +0000" stop="20250919033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Sketch Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"Family Sketch Show. Originally aired on 05/04/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919033000 +0000" stop="20250919043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Scandalous Sculptor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Scandal rocks the art world when a model is found dead, presumably murdered by the jealous wife of a sculptor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919043500 +0000" stop="20250919050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Fugitive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An old man possessing the power of transformation tries to help a crippled little girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919050500 +0000" stop="20250919053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Escape To Sonoita</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Two kidnappers find a tanker in the middle of the desert and decide to make their escape in it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919053500 +0000" stop="20250919060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Hooked</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A man schemes with a young woman to get rid of his wealthy wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919060500 +0000" stop="20250919070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Wasn’t There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An old adversary from Mannix's time serving in the Korean War, whom he thought was dead, sets out to kill him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919070500 +0000" stop="20250919080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Missing At Fl307</sub-title>
    <desc>"An ex-convict boards an airplane in Atlanta for a reunion with his daughter but when the plane lands he's nowhere to be found."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919080500 +0000" stop="20250919090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Design For Madness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby tries to help her emotionally disturbed niece when she's suspected of murdering her husband and his lawyer during memory lapses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919090000 +0000" stop="20250919093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big High</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly businessman concerned about the welfare of his grandchild informs Friday and Gannon that his daughter and son-in-law are using marijuana regularly. The young couple make no apologies for their lifestyle, which inevitably leads to disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919093000 +0000" stop="20250919100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Ad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con named Steve Deal contacts Friday and Gannon when a classified ad that he placed, offering to do "anything" for money, results in an offer to commit murder. Friday goes undercover as Deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919100000 +0000" stop="20250919103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 23: Pig Is A Three Letter Word</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers are subjected to verbal abuse when they arrest armed robbers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919103000 +0000" stop="20250919110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 83 -- A Different Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An older husband complains about his wife and friend's noisy karate practice. A hit and run traffic accident looks looks like a homicide. The officers use their investigative skills to locate the suspect and arrest him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919110000 +0000" stop="20250919120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Masquerade Ball</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony recieve a mysterious invitation."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919120000 +0000" stop="20250919123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Younger Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver decides to join the basketball team but finds himself trying to live up to Wally's performance. However, after not making the team, Beaver allows his family to believe that he did.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919123000 +0000" stop="20250919130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Typewriter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Seeing an ad for typewriters on sale, Beaver talks his parents into letting him get one as long as he learns how to use it. However, Beaver discovers learning to type is not as easy as it looks and soon finds himself making a deal with the shady Eddie Haskell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919130000 +0000" stop="20250919140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Black-eyed Blonde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>A visit from an attractive blonde sporting a black eye segues into a case concerning a wealthy man's long-lost grandson and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919140000 +0000" stop="20250919150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Madam  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a blackmailing call girl is charged with murder, Matlock is hired to bring the real killer to justice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919150000 +0000" stop="20250919160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Pig Woman Of Sparta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>It seems that a serial killer has been burying his victims in a wooded area owned by a wealthy hermit that Virgil refers to as "Sparta's Howard Hughes". Suspicion immediately falls on an eccentric woman who lives in the woods with her pigs and chases away trespassers with a shotgun. The officers ask the landowner's disturbed son for help and Bubba is surprised to find that a woman he attended high school with is working as the man's "nurse". Also Parker and Sweet compete with one another to solve the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919160000 +0000" stop="20250919170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Captive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Corabeth Godsey feels trapped by her unchanging life on Walton's Mountain</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919170000 +0000" stop="20250919180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Hanging Of Newly O'brien</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly attempts to save a hillbilly's life by using drastic measures. The family wants to hang Newly after the man dies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919180000 +0000" stop="20250919190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hoss helps send a man to prison, his wife insists that Hoss should be made responsible for their son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919190000 +0000" stop="20250919193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sharpshooter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas McCain and his son, Mark, arrive in North Fork, New Mexico. Looking to start a new life, they come across a ranch that is to their liking, which is for sale. Lucas enters a Turkey Shoot in hopes of winning the down payment for the ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919193000 +0000" stop="20250919200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Home Ranch</sub-title>
    <desc>"Two hired hands of a wealthy cattleman, who has been using the ranch for grazing his cattle, demand that Lucas move out. When Lucas refuses, he is beaten and dragged and then the ranch house is burned down."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919200000 +0000" stop="20250919210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Eleanor Culhane Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>"Flint goes to visit Eleanor Culhane, an old flame of his who had been married to a notorious gunman. He finds everyone in the town she lives in shunning her, and unwilling to discuss her, because they blame her for her husband's misdeeds and the shame he caused the town. When Flint finds her they begin to rekindle their romance. But then her husband, thought dead for the last five years, shows up in town. And Flint realizes there is another side to Eleanor that he was unaware of as well."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919210000 +0000" stop="20250919220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Bottom Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Paramedics out in the field begin to question the judgment of overcautious Dr. Morton who believes in acting strictly by the book. The firemen respond to a complaint of severe back pain. A man with phosphorous burns on his arm and a boy hit in the head with a baseball are treated at the hospital. While the firemen respond to a case of difficult breathing, the victim’s neighbor drowns in a hot tub. Vince is involved in a traffic accident and goes crazy due to a head injury, pulling his gun on Johnny.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919220000 +0000" stop="20250919223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is confronted by two crises: Colonel Potter's mare, Sophie, mysteriously disappears from her corral, and Hawkeye and B.J. find themselves with a young Korean boy on their hands, who is trying to avoid conscription into the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919223000 +0000" stop="20250919230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Young And The Restless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lecture on the latest techniques by a young surgeon from Tokyo, and a later demonstration of his surgical skill, turns Winchester into a drunk and Potter into an invalid, whilst bringing home to Hawkeye and B.J. that they are out of touch with new medical practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919230000 +0000" stop="20250919233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips Is Back In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar, who is smitten with the cute new nurse, Linda Nugent, relies on Hawkeye's expertise on how to cope with the situation. Hot Lips, meanwhile, celebrates her just-granted divorce by taking a step that arouses Colonel Potter's ire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919233000 +0000" stop="20250920000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>C*a*v*e</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th evacuation to a nearby cave to avoid US artillery fire on a Chinese target poses problems for Hawkeye, who has a claustrophobia problem of which Colonel Potter is not aware.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920000000 +0000" stop="20250920003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Prisoner Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lady prisoner woos Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920003000 +0000" stop="20250920010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has Mayberry worried when he buys a car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920010000 +0000" stop="20250920013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Cimarron Drip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is hoping to get a part in Dash Riprock’s new TV series, getting a whole new image. Little does Dash know, the show, which is a rehash of every successful show since 1948, didn’t make it, and the female lead, Debbie Dimples, has impossible demands. Drysdale suggests that they use a monkey, Elly’s chimp Cousin, Bessie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920013000 +0000" stop="20250920020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, Pow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>On maneuvers, Sgt. Carter gives Gomer false information, hoping he'll be captured by the enemy camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920020000 +0000" stop="20250920023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Get Fit Or Go Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink to get back in shape so he won't be sent to the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920023000 +0000" stop="20250920030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Fat Hermann, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get a trainload of stolen paintings back to London, but things get complicated when Marya uses Schultz to impersonate Reich Marshall Goehring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920030000 +0000" stop="20250920033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guest Jim Nabors. Originally aired on 09/14/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920033000 +0000" stop="20250920043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sleepy Slayer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man is accused of killing his employer, who still owed him $50,000 for an accident years before, it's up to Mason to find the real killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920043500 +0000" stop="20250920050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>To her parents' horror, a six-year-old girl vanishes into the fourth dimension after rolling under her bed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920050500 +0000" stop="20250920053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Young One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenager’s desire to be free leads her to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920053500 +0000" stop="20250920060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Doubtful Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A man relates an unusual situation to his doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920060500 +0000" stop="20250920070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Principle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Two elderly spinster sisters are determined to prosecute a traffic violator. There's only one problem: The man also is a syndicate killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920070500 +0000" stop="20250920080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Set-up</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is a victim of mistaken identity and later almost killed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920080500 +0000" stop="20250920090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Girl On The Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A runaway girl discovers that the glitter of the drug world has a deadly underside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920090000 +0000" stop="20250920093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A U.S. government top-secret camera falls out a plane and lands in the Shady Rest. Little does anyone know, the curious device could bring them "explosive" problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920093000 +0000" stop="20250920100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Mayor Of Hooterville</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe decides to run as the first mayor of Hooterville.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920100000 +0000" stop="20250920103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lib And Let Lib</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Troubles are following everyone after the women’s lib movement ended. Elly and Granny return home to the mansion, while Jethro still believes he is Japanese and the women should serve him because women should wait on man. And at the bank, the secretaries are working on better working conditions, but get bullied by Banzai, who is trying to get new girls from Japan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920103000 +0000" stop="20250920110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly, The Working Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly gets a job as a secretary at Mr. Drysdale’s bank to ensure proper treatment of the girls working there. But Granny makes her look like a flapper and teaches her wiggle walking, eye rolling and lap setting. Drysdale throws her out, but after he realizes it is his largest depositor’s daughter, brings her back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920110000 +0000" stop="20250920113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Plumbing Is A “pipe”, Her Honor The Mare, A Date To Skate</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye visits Olive Oyl and discovers her home in turmoil because of a broken water pipe., Popeye's nephews decide to take a horse home when it's rejected by a glue factory., It's Olive's first visit to a skating rink, and Popeye accidentally crashes into the pillar to which she is clinging. Popeye manages to rescue Olive in an amusing climax."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920113000 +0000" stop="20250920120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tot Watchers, Early Bird Dood It, Sufferin' Cats</sub-title>
    <desc>"A babysitter more concerned with the phone leaves Tom and Jerry to watch the baby., The worm enlists a cat to get rid of the bird chasing him but the bird turns out to be too smart for the cat., Jerry is a prize to be won between Tom and an alley cat because neither feline wants to share him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920120000 +0000" stop="20250920130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Dizzy Acrobat, Robinson Gruesome, Crazy Mixed Up Pup, The Reckless Driver, The Overture To William Tell, Dizzy Kitty, Who's Cookin Who?</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody tries to sneak into the circus., Chilly rides a melting iceberg to a south seas island, where Smedley has been stranded for 28 years., A man and his dog take on each other's attributes after an accident., Woody Woodpecker tries to renew his driver's license with a grumpy officer., Obstacles arise as Wally conducts an orchestra., Andy and his father try to groom an alley cat for a Cat Show., After failing to store food for winter, Woody attempts to turn the story of Little Red Riding Hood on its head by luring and eating a wolf. It turns out, they both want to eat each other."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920130000 +0000" stop="20250920140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Million Hare, Tweetie Pie, The Foghorn Leghorn, Rhapsody Rabbit, Out And Out Rout, Woolen Under Where, A Witch's Tangled Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"A television show is having a contest to see who can get to the television station first, Bugs or Daffy. , When Tweety is brought in from the cold, the owner warns Sylvester to leave him alone. , Henery Hawk, determined to hunt chickens, goes down to Foghorn's barnyard. Henery Hawk misinterprets the dog for a chicken and Foghorn tries to set him straight. , Bugs Bunny attempts to perform a piano solo of Liszt's "Second Hungarian Rhapsody" but is foiled by a little mouse. , Coyote tries many different ways to catch Road Runner but is never able to. , It is another day at work for Ralph Wolf and Sam Sheepdog. , In search of poetic inspiration, William Shakespeare comes across the castle of Macbeth and finds Witch Hazel chasing Bugs Bunny therein. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920140000 +0000" stop="20250920150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Egyptian Queen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Agent Artemus Gordon and the curator of the San Francisco Museum are set upon in the Egyptian exhibit by three men wearing gas masks. When agents West and Mr. Heisel, the Egyptian government's representative, enter the room, they are also attacked. After regaining consciousness, the men discover that a priceless ruby has been stolen from the eye of the statue of Sun God, Ra. Commissioned by Miasmin, an Egyptian Princess, to recover the gem, West and Gordon trace a ransom note to a waterfront bar where Gordon poses as a sea captain. At the bar, West recognizes one of his assailants at the museum. The man identifies himself as Jason and indicates that Rosie, a beautiful young dancer at the bar, is wearing the ruby on her toe. Unfortunately, Rosie vanishes before West can make a move.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920150000 +0000" stop="20250920170000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke IV: The Long Ride</title>
    <desc>"Retired marshal Matt Dillon must clear his name after a lying witness makes him wanted: dead or alive."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920170000 +0000" stop="20250920180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Crooked Mile</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's whip-wielding father does not approve of her romance with Quint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920180000 +0000" stop="20250920190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Bushwhacked!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe is found shot in the back and delirious by a pair of cowboys roaming the prairie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920190000 +0000" stop="20250920193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>End Of A Young Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is forced to give refuge to Will Fulton, a young bank robber who was injured while saving Mark's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920193000 +0000" stop="20250920200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Marshal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah Torrance, a once famous lawman, is introduced as a drunken derelict who stumbles into North Fork. Micah, nursing an arm crippled in a gunfight, is hired by Lucas to help out at the ranch. Three outlaws ride into town looking for revenge against Micah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920200000 +0000" stop="20250920210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Damon's Road: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After escaping from the railroad builder, Favor attempts to get his drovers back, but they are set on being railroaders. Favor must hatch a scheme to get his men back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920210000 +0000" stop="20250920213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Teacher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin defends a schoolmistress who's being theatened for teaching about war crimes that took place during the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920213000 +0000" stop="20250920220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Chain Gang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After being arrested for a minor offense, Josh is put on the chain gang and put to work on the local mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920220000 +0000" stop="20250921000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Mummy's Dummies, Dopey Dicks, Don't Throw That Knife, Cuckoo On A Choo Choo, Blunder Boys, Studio Stoops</sub-title>
    <desc>"Set in ancient Egypt, the Stooges run a used chariot lot where they unload defective chariots on unsuspecting customers.  When they gyp the head of the palace guard, they're brought to the palace to be executed, but instead become royal chamberlains after curing the King's toothache.  When they recover some tax money stolen by a corrupt official, the King rewards them with marriage to his daughter.  After getting a look at the ugly crone, Moe and Larry select Shemp to be the groom. , It's mindless fun at its best when the Stooges meet a mad scientist in search of a human brain for his headless mechanical man.  , The Stooges are hired by a movie studio as publicity men.  Their first assignment is to get publicity for Dolly Devore, a pretty starlet.  They fake a kidnapping, but the cops won't believe their story.  Then the girl is really kidnapped and the Stooges must come to the rescue.  Shemp winds up hanging out a tenth story window on an extending telephone. , The Stooges become census takers and wind up in the apartment of a lady whose husband is both jealous and a knife thrower.  When the husband arrives home, the boys try to hide, but are discovered, and after dodging some knives, leave on the run. , Larry and Shemp are living in a stolen railroad car.  Larry wants to marry his girlfriend, but she won't consent until Shemp marries her sister.  Shemp however, is constantly drunk and in love with "Carry", an imaginary giant canary.  Moe is an investigator from the railroad, sent to discover how the car was stolen from a moving train.  Moe is also in love with Shemp's girl.  Shemp winds up with both women, but still prefers his imaginary canary. , A parody of the television series Dragnet. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921000000 +0000" stop="20250921023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Tarantula</sub-title>
    <desc>"This classic science fiction film featuring Academy Award winning screen legend Clint Eastwood tells the story of a scientist who, while researching the effects of a new synthetic nutrient, releases a giant spider in the American Southwest.  A quintessential exercise in pulp horror, "Tarantula" is the drive-in, monster flick that still thrills and chills. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921023000 +0000" stop="20250921030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Give 'em The Axe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>An explosion renders Batman and Robin unconscious and believed dead by the Riddler. When the Dynamic Duo comes to, it's up to Robin to sneak into the museum and stop the plot to raid an ancient sarcophagus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921030000 +0000" stop="20250921040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Conscience Of The King</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk is one of the last survivors who can identify a mass killer lurking among a Shakespearean troupe aboard the Enterprise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921040000 +0000" stop="20250921043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Dagger Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Clark and Lois are umpires in a treasure hunt on Dagger Island. One of the heirs is ruthless in his quest and endangers the rest of the party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921043000 +0000" stop="20250921050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Blackmail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Inspector Henderson pretends to take a bribe so he can catch a crime boss. Superman intervenes to clear the cop's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921050000 +0000" stop="20250921060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Keeper: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Keeper, played by Michael Rennie, is a zookeeper of sorts. He wants to take the children and add them to his collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921060000 +0000" stop="20250921070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Werewolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Volcanic radioactivity turns a scientist into a werewolf who threatens the Seaview. Meanwhile, Nelson and Crane attempt to snuff out the volcanic island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921070000 +0000" stop="20250921080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Every Dog Needs A Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When Clipper is injured by a giant dog, the Earthlings must take him to a pet store owner, but his employee isn't so sympathetic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921080000 +0000" stop="20250921090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Idol Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1519, Tony and Doug vow to slow down Cortez's conquest of Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921090000 +0000" stop="20250921100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Believers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The aliens plot to eliminate Vincent once and for all, attacking a group of "believers".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921100000 +0000" stop="20250921110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Home Of The Hawk</sub-title>
    <desc>"A wagon falls on the leg of a settler,"Metcalf". He and his daughter are assisted by Adams,who lets them stay with him. She likes all the animals, mainly a hawk and the next day,despite her dad's warning,goes out exploring on her own."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921110000 +0000" stop="20250921113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Roundup On The Rupununi</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin travels to Guyana to join Stan Brock in a cattle drive.  Soon they are aware of a jaguar marauding the herd.  There is only one thing to do if the drive is to continue … catch the jaguar."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921113000 +0000" stop="20250921120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Cougar Mountain</sub-title>
    <desc>"High in the Rocky Mountains a puma and here three cubs end their first summer together.  Soon snow falls and the animals begin their annual trek down to a lower valley."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921120000 +0000" stop="20250921123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Beneath Kilimanjaro</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beneath Kilimanjaro lies the Amboseli Game Reserve, last refuge for the remnants of the great cattle and wild animal herds that once roamed east Africa.  Marlin and Jim seek a way for coexistence of the animals in the Amboseli."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921123000 +0000" stop="20250921130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Leopards Of Sawai Madipur</sub-title>
    <desc>"Rajastan India lies in an ancient, deserted castle.  This is the story of a family of leopards who now occupy this castle."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921130000 +0000" stop="20250921133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Arctic Adventure</sub-title>
    <desc>"A trip to the top of the world … above the Arctic Circle, north of Hudson Bay for a polar bear hunt and a walrus capture."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921133000 +0000" stop="20250921140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Lightning</sub-title>
    <desc>"A mother cheetah leads her playful cubs over the vast Rhodesian veldt teaching them the ways of defense and hunting."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921140000 +0000" stop="20250921143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Career Fever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg writes a class paper about wanting to become an architect like his dad. Mike reads the paper and is ecstatic and encouraging, but is Greg's heart really in it?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921143000 +0000" stop="20250921150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>To Move Or Not To Move</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>With constant complaints about the size of the house bombarding Mike and Carol, Mike puts the house up for sale and looks into buying a new one. It isn't long after that that the house appears to be haunted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921150000 +0000" stop="20250921153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Kiss Me Sickly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie asks Richie to watch after his girl, Denise, while he's out of town at a demolition derby. Denise, upon hearing what Fonzie's asked Richie to do, decides to test Richie's trustworthiness. Richie succumbs to temptation and makes out with Denise at Inspiriation Point, later finding out that she has mononucleosis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921153000 +0000" stop="20250921160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Hi, Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Just when Laverne and Shirley thought they'd have some peace and quiet, look who moves into the building—Lenny and Squiggy are their new second-floor neighbors!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921160000 +0000" stop="20250921163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Song Festers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer's singing voice surprises everyone, especially Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921163000 +0000" stop="20250921170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Ricky And Fred Are Tv Fans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>With Ricky and Fred glued to a TV fight, their wives go to the local cafe, where service is so slow that Lucy makes change for herself at the cash register and the girls are arrested. They finally prove their innocence and get home to husbands who didn't know they were gone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921170000 +0000" stop="20250921173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Marine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward comes down hard on Wally after he comes home two hours late, this fuels June and Ward's suspicions that Wally is contemplating joining the Merchant Marines. June had discovered some pamphlets hidden in his dresser drawer. However, little does anyone know, Wally has been getting the information for Lumpy who's seriously thinking of joining.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921173000 +0000" stop="20250921180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Versus Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets a new girl in his class and is instantly smitten. He begins walking her home from school but he soon realizes that the girl has an agenda on her mind. Her sole purpose is to get close to Beaver in order to get close to Wally. This leads Beaver to accuse Wally of stealing his girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921180000 +0000" stop="20250921183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Girls From Grun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finish dining with their Grunion, a surfer boy and a girl, and tell the captives they will let them go. Jethro wants to keep his captured girl, but Jed let’s the two go. At the bank, Drysdale, who tells Helen she must take the blame for his stupid mistakes, decides to get his former secretary back. Helen goes to the beach to try to get Jane back, and finds out the Clampetts still believe Grunion are people, a poor excuse, but people nonetheless.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921183000 +0000" stop="20250921190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly, The Secretary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts receive a telegram that says Louellen Aden is coming out to California. When Jed tells Jethro about this, they figure out that she wants to marry Jethro. He gets scared and runs away. Meanwhile, Elly is learning to be a secretary, but is not very good at it. She and Miss Jane go to bring Louellen to the Clampett mansion, and the family learns that she has changed into a lovely young lady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921190000 +0000" stop="20250921193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Seer Gilligan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan discovers an island bush that produces seeds that when eaten give a person the ability to read the minds of others.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921193000 +0000" stop="20250921200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Love Me, Love My Skipper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The Howell's plan a party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921200000 +0000" stop="20250921203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Now Hear This  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Vint installs baby-monitoring intercoms in the house, the Harpers begin eavesdropping on each other—and it isn't long before everyone is upset!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921203000 +0000" stop="20250921210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Tri-state's Most Wanted  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama believes she's fallen for a wanted criminal, she decides to capture him herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921210000 +0000" stop="20250921220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>I Don't Play Anymore</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Gopher thinks he recognizes a woman; a pianist debates ending his retirement; a man tries to claim workers' compensation for insanity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921220000 +0000" stop="20250921223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Shoplifters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Weaver's Department store is being robbed, presumably by shoplifters. Barney poses as a mannequin to catch a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921223000 +0000" stop="20250921230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Jeremy Beaver- Hip Hop Memorabilia</sub-title>
    <desc>"Music producer and collector, Jeremy Beaver, started the National Hip Hop Museum to share the culture and history of hip-hop with America, and now he’s sharing it with Collector’s Call, including the turntables that started it all, DJ Kool Herc’s equipment used to invent the genre in 1973, and a collection from the legendary Sugarhill Gang, introduced by member, Master Gee himself. Expert and music historian, JayQuan, attempts a trade with a record-breaking record of his own."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921230000 +0000" stop="20250921233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rally Round The Flagg, Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The sinister Colonel Flagg pops up at the 4077th again, playing his usual spy games, convinced that Hawkeye is a communist sympathizer after he saves the life of a North Korean soldier. Also, an American soldier is less than impressed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921233000 +0000" stop="20250922000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Preventive Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On a sub-note, Klinger plays the part of a voodoo practitioner to try and get out of the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922000000 +0000" stop="20250922003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike's Pains</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike must decide if he wants to be in the delivery room during the birth of the baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922003000 +0000" stop="20250922010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Chain Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's refusal to particpate in a chain letter triggers a string of unlikely events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922010000 +0000" stop="20250922013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike Faces Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike becomes the sole support of a growing family when Gloria loses her job because of her pregnancy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922013000 +0000" stop="20250922020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Breaks Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie feels abandoned after Edith begins to volunteer part-time at the Sunshine Home for the Elderly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922020000 +0000" stop="20250922023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Cass Elliot And Pat Paulsen</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Cass Elliot and Pat Paulsen. Originally aired on 09/21/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922023000 +0000" stop="20250922030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nanette Fabray And Ken Berry</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nanette Fabray and Ken Berry. Originally aired on 10/12/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922030000 +0000" stop="20250922033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Sally And The Lab Technician</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura sets Sally up with a shy cousin and a disastrous dinner date ensues.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922033000 +0000" stop="20250922040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Washington Vs. The Bunny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob has the worst dilemma: choose to travel on business or see his son's school play.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922040000 +0000" stop="20250922043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Ralph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, after making a suggestion at work, is laid off. Alice decides to take a job as a secretary, but tells her boss that Ralph is her brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922043000 +0000" stop="20250922053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Bard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An untalented would-be writer's career takes off when the ghost of William Sharespeare writes his script.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922053000 +0000" stop="20250922060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Very Moral Theft</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A desperate man tries to save his company from bankruptcy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922060000 +0000" stop="20250922070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>A Ghost Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Howard Bainbridge, a chemical warfare expert who defected to the East, was contaminated by his own experiments and then returned back to the U.S. and his family manor, where his father (a paranoid arch-conservative) had him killed and the body buried.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922070000 +0000" stop="20250922080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Man Picked A Lemon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a ranch hand on a California citrus farm, the owner, Leland Hagerman, suddenly dies in an accident and the man's racist and sadistic son, Blaine, arrives to stake his claim to the place and sees everyone as expendable, including Kimble wh</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922080000 +0000" stop="20250922090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Past Imperfect</sub-title>
    <desc>"Private investigator Harry Orwell helps a young woman save the life she has made for herself from a ruthless man out of her past."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922090000 +0000" stop="20250922093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman real estate agent is missing and turns up dead in a vacant home. The detectives' one suspect, the woman's ex-boyfriend, is cleared; then credit card bills for purchases made after the woman's death start appearing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922093000 +0000" stop="20250922100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A purse-snatching dog? This is the case Friday and Gannon must solve. Making things more difficult, victims give different descriptions of the four-legged thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922100000 +0000" stop="20250922103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 103 -- A Sound Like Thunder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and his date join Reed and his expecting wife on a weekend trip to a ghost town, but soon they cross paths with a dangerous motorcycle gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922103000 +0000" stop="20250922110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 63 -- Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed's wife is in the hospital expecting their first child, and Reed soon regrets his decision to report for work as usual. Out on patrol, they encounter a drunken man directing traffic, chase down a robbery suspect, investigate the theft of money from washing machines and become involved in a minor traffic accident that results in a major delay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922110000 +0000" stop="20250922120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Fall Equinox</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922120000 +0000" stop="20250922123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Yard Birds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward doesn't take any excuses when he puts his foot down and demands that Wally and Beaver clean the yard. They each reluctantly cancel their plans with Richard and Eddie and get to work but soon find themselves with distractions. This causes them to miss the deadline to call the hauler who is suppose to take all the yard waste away and this leads them to pay Eddie and Lumpy to take care of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922123000 +0000" stop="20250922130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tennis, Anyone</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally finds himself smack dab in the middle of a lover's quarrel when a woman tries to make her estranged boyfriend jealous by continually making tennis dates with Wally. Wally finds himself in an awkward position when the boyfriend threatens him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922130000 +0000" stop="20250922140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Terrified Typist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>While a woman is searching the office of the South African Diamond Company, George Baxter enters to meet Walter Lumis and Duane Jefferson. He notices things in disarray and tries to question the woman, but she makes her escape and seeks out Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922140000 +0000" stop="20250922150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Nowhere To Turn: Part 1  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends himself against a murder charge after a judge who issued him a contempt citation is found dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922150000 +0000" stop="20250922160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie is kidnapped and Virgil believes that Tom Dugan is involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922160000 +0000" stop="20250922170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Illusion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Verdie Foster's daughter Esther returns to the mountain. After graduating with honors from college, she cannot find a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922170000 +0000" stop="20250922180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Jailer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Six years after her husband's hanging, Ma Stone plots her revenge against Matt Dillon by first kidnapping Kitty to use as a lure and then jailing Matt with the intention to hang him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922180000 +0000" stop="20250922190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Rock-a-bye Hoss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss is reluctantly made to judge a contest for the most beautiful baby in Virginia City.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922190000 +0000" stop="20250922193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's uncle, Johnny Gibb, a big-time rodeo rider, comes to visit. While Mark idolizes his uncle, Lucas discovers that Johnny is on the run from the law for an Express Office robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922193000 +0000" stop="20250922200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eight Hours To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Judge Burton seeks "justice" against the hangman who hanged his son; the judge who sentenced his son; and Lucas, the man who caught his son. When Judge Burton discovers that Lucas has a son, he decides that the best way to serve justice is an eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, a son for a son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922200000 +0000" stop="20250922210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Chalice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>"An Italian immigrant couple needs help in transporting water for their grapevines to California. Unfortunately, the two men who offer the use of their wagon plan to steal the treasure they've heard the immigrants are carrying in return for their services."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922210000 +0000" stop="20250922220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Firehouse Quintet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Station 51 basketball team qualifies for the semi-finals. The paramedics rescue victims at a gas explosion. While at basketball practice, the firemen treat an injured gymnast. The night before the big game the firemen get very little sleep: they respond to a number of emergencies, including a workman trapped at a studio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922220000 +0000" stop="20250922223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At Rosie's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A typical day in the life of Rosie's bar, complete with AWOL problem drinkers, a bound and gagged Winchester and a gambling scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922223000 +0000" stop="20250922230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ain't Love Grand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The impossible happens for the snobbish Charles when he shares an emotional experience with Klinger, who discovers a US nurse, Debbie, finds him and his bizarre attire attractive, while Charles succumbs to the exotic charms of a Korean girl, called Sooni, who he meets at Rosie's Bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922230000 +0000" stop="20250922233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Talk of a post-war reunion gives B.J. an idea—planning a present-day stateside gathering of 4077th families. He continues to obsess with the idea even under the duress of bug-out instigated by a Chinese breakthrough. Also, Klinger fears that the party will blow his cover, as his mother doesn't know he's stationed in Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922233000 +0000" stop="20250923000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Too Many Cooks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy foot soldier, "Look Out Below" Conway, finds the quickest way to the crew's heart, boosting morale at the 4077th by cooking gourmet delights. Only Colonel Potter, burdened with a personal crisis, is immune from the high spirits enveloping the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923000000 +0000" stop="20250923003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Vacation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A grumpy Andy agrees to take a few days off and heads up to the lake to relax. Barney and Gomer are in charge, and manage to capture (and lose) an escaped convict who hides in the same woods where Andy just happens to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923003000 +0000" stop="20250923010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is convinced that Andy saved his life by putting out a small fire at the filling station. He then begins to repay Andy by becoming his servant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923010000 +0000" stop="20250923013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Corn Pone Picassos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mrs. Drysdale buys a statue named "Ecstasy," which is nothing but a huge pile of metal scraps, the Clampetts decide to get involved in art to help their neighbor in the contest she is entering. Jed and Jethro buy an authentic Rembrandt, a Sam Rembrandt, and Granny uses her artist cousin as influence to paint Mrs. Drysdale a for-sure winner, thinking the statue she bought has no chance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923013000 +0000" stop="20250923020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, Civilian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>When Sgt. Carter orders him to take a furlough, Gomer becomes a civilian employee at the base.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923020000 +0000" stop="20250923023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Assassin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon interferes as Hogan tries to help a defecting scientist, whom they were ordered to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923023000 +0000" stop="20250923030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Cupid Comes To Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan helps Klink fall in love with General Burkhalter's sister to get his mind off not being promoted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923030000 +0000" stop="20250923033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Pat Carroll And Art Carney</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Pat Carroll and Art Carney. Originally aired on 01/04/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923033000 +0000" stop="20250923043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Betrayed Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A recently widowed women becomes tangled in a web of suspicion when she hastily remarries a fortune-hunting Frenchman. When the Frenchman's ex-wife comes looking for him, he turns up shot dead in a swimming pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923043500 +0000" stop="20250923050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Person Or Persons Unknown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A man wakes up one morning to discover that no one knows who he is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923050500 +0000" stop="20250923053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Contest For Aaron Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man devotes his entire stay at a summer camp to modeling a one-armed clay knight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923053500 +0000" stop="20250923060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Five-forty-eight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A philandering senior manager finds himself being stalked by a previous secretary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923060500 +0000" stop="20250923070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of The Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In order to help break up a narcotics ring, Peggy is recruited to pose as a prostitute.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923070500 +0000" stop="20250923080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Investigator</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is called in to investigate police corruption by the mayor of a Midwestern town."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923080500 +0000" stop="20250923090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Indoctrination Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>While on the search for a missing girl, Betty uncovers a center for white slavers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923090000 +0000" stop="20250923093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Pyramid Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A female con-artist uses an evangelistic approach to lure buyers into her pyramid scheme. The Bunco division can't charge her with false advertising, so they prosecute her for operating a lottery.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
